Hello Friends Welcome to AK Update Vacancy
YouTube Channel.  Today I am going to
give you some information, all
VLE brothers please watch the video till the end
so that you can understand the entire video process by
process.  Today I am going to talk about
how we will do third party insurance of bike or motor from ICI Lampard,
today I will give you complete
information about this.  Stay tuned to this video and
if you understand any video after watching it, then
please like the video and
send it to your BL brother so that
he can get complete information about how to do insurance in CSC.   First of all
we have to go to our computer
screen.  There we have to go to Chrome
browser.  You have to
login and keep your CSC ID inside the Chrome browser.
There we have to
go to third party insurance in the insurance option.
After going to third party insurance, you have to
see the service there.  ICI Lambod
Service It is marked.  Look,
you have to click on this mark here, click here.
After clicking, you will be asked for ID and password.
Here you have to enter your CSC ID and
password and fill the capture code and
click on login.   On
clicking login, you will get the
dashboard of ICI Lambod.  There you have to
click on third party and enter your vehicle
registration number here.  As soon as you
enter the vehicle registration number, the
complete details of the vehicle will open
and you have to
click on Get Quit here.
Only after clicking on Get Quit, you will get complete information about the vehicle and only then will
its premium
be told to you as to how much the vehicle insurance will cost.
Here I am telling you about compressive
because the third
party option is over in the bus vehicle.  Therefore, it
is mandatory to do both of these in this vehicle.  That's why
I am talking about compressive.  There
are two options in compressive third party.
You can click third party instead of compressive.
PAN card number has to be entered here.  Here you have to
enter the customer's date of birth or mobile number, email ID and address.
Here you have to fill the landmark area pin code date city
state city sorry here
and click on same here,
after this you have to go to the next step.  Have to
move to the next step.   As soon as you
go to the next step, you have to
enter the vehicle number, changes and engine
number here.  All this will start showing you the
date on which the vehicle was manufactured.
You will start seeing this information in it.
It will also tell whether your loan is in cash or the vehicle
is in cash and here you have to
fill the details of the nominee and here his age
and here his relation, what is his relation with the person whose bike or
vehicle it is.
After this you have to click on Generate Proposal.   As soon as you
click on Generate Proposal, the
entire data of this type will open to you.  Vehicle
number, what is the premium of the vehicle?
And here you have to click on Agree.  As soon as you
click on Agree, you can
see the complete details here.  Click on Agree and
here on Make Payment.   As soon as you
click on Make Payment, you get the
option of Proceed and Cancel in Make Payment.
If the data is not clear then you
can cancel.  No, click on proceed.
Clicking on Proceed will
take you directly to your CSC dashboard.
Where the password and transaction ID of the CSC ID have to be
entered.  He will
take you there and
leave you there.  There you have to enter the CSC
ID password and
its
transaction password and then
enter the transaction password here and select
Make Payment and click on it.   As soon as
you click on Max Payment, a
receipt will be generated.  You have to
print out that receipt and give it to the customer.  It has to be
given to the customer.  If you like the video,
please like and
subscribe to our channel.